<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Alex Lynd on</title><link>/contributors/alex-lynd/</link><description>Recent content in Alex Lynd on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 00:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/contributors/alex-lynd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Stealthy GPS Tracker &amp; Drive-by Telemetry Using Open Wi-Fi</title><link>/Stealthy-Drive-by-GPS-Tracker-ESP8266/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>/Stealthy-Drive-by-GPS-Tracker-ESP8266/</guid><description>⚠️ This project is still in progress! Check my blog and GitHub for the latest updates &amp;amp; upcoming documentation. Low-Cost Tracking Challenge In a recent Hak5 episode, I took part in a challenge to track our elusive friend, Irish, and determine the various places he visited throughout the day.
Since low-cost hardware &amp;amp; disposable signals intelligence is a core part of my projects, I challenged myself to create a tracker in the smallest practical footprint, and designed a $10 device that uses only Wi-Fi to provide location updates once planted on Irish&amp;rsquo;s car.</description></item><item><title>Easy Data Exfiltration with CanaryTokens</title><link>/blog/easy-data-exfiltration-with-canarytokens/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 11:07:26 -0700</pubDate><guid>/blog/easy-data-exfiltration-with-canarytokens/</guid><description>Overview If you&amp;rsquo;re just getting started with data exfiltration, it might not be practical to set up an entire webserver or local environment just to try out some simple techniques, like web request exfiltration.
In my Hak5 episode, I created a simple proof-of-concept using an online tool called CanaryTokens, to demonstrate how simple it is to remotely exfiltrate a Linux password using a single command.
Using a keystroke injection tool called the USB Nugget, I created a payload that demonstrates this sneaky attack in seconds - but if you dont have one, you can still practice the exfiltration techniques with your web browser.</description></item></channel></rss>